[sin traducir] was the function. Now, you may say
[sin traducir] say well it's obvious wasn't always obvious.
[sin traducir] obvious. The idea of a function of a as an
como abstracción no surgió hasta las décadas de 1940 y 1950
E incluso entonces se consideraba
ser algo asombroso
idea controvertida. ¿Por qué es ese el caso?
caso porque cada vez que haces una llamada a función
Todo requiere dos o tres más
[sin traducir] instructions and those were in the days of
[sin traducir] of computing back then, extremely
[sin traducir] expensive. So we had this this
[sin traducir] This tradeoff between do we build things
[sin traducir] that serve our machines do we build
[sin traducir] build things that serve the needs of our humans.
[sin traducir] I was at this battle, but in those
[sin traducir] In those days, the machines were far more
[sin traducir] more expensive than our humans, and so a lot of what we happen in
[sin traducir] happened in software engineering was to optimize the needs for the
[sin traducir] for the machine, not the humans themselves.
[sin traducir] yourselves. Well, with
[sin traducir] With the advent of micro-miniaturization, we had from the mainframe
[sin traducir] mainframes, we suddenly had many
[sin traducir] minicomputers like the PDP-11
[sin traducir] oven uh 60 series uh we had
[sin traducir] microcomputers as well